Hammersley Hill
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Hammersley Hill, 2.1.4.1
  - Hammersley Hill: L. T. [Lowell Thomas] personal [negative images distorted], circa 1930s; 2 (Box 1568)
    - L.T. personal, sitting on front porch at C.B.F. [Clover Brook Farm], 2
    - L.T. riding at C.B.F. [Clover Brook Farm], 3
  - Hammersley Hill: Mrs. L. T. (Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas) personal [negative images distorted], circa 1935 - 1940; 3 (Box 1568)
    - Mrs. L.T. [Frances Ryan Thomas] on horse, 1
    - Mrs. L.T. [Frances Ryan Thomas] and dog, 2
    - Mrs. L.T. [Frances Ryan Thomas] and dog, 3
  - Hammersley Hill: Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], circa 1930s; 4 (Box 1568)
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] and boys at Locust Farm, 1
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] riding hay rake at Locust Farm, 2
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] and boys with horse and hay rack, 3
    - Miss Richards with Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] and children, 4
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] and boys pitching hay, 5
    - Locust Farm-house, 6
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] and two children, 7
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] and boy and calf, 8
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] and two dogs, 9
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] and group of children, 10
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] with boy and cart, 11
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] with children and man, 12
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] with group of boys and girls, 13
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] and boys on fallen tree, 14
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] + dog, 15
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] + dog, 16
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] + dog, 17
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] + dog, 18
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] + dog, 19
    - Group at farm when Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] was under five years of age: Including Mrs. L.T. [Frances Ryan Thomas], Pherbia + Sonny, 20
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] watching boys swimming, 21
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] + little girl sitting on large stone, 22
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] and little girl, 23
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] and children, 24
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 25
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 26
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 27
  - Hammersley Hill: Pawling - homes, circa 1930s; 5 (Box 1568)
    - Pawling school scene, Route 22, 1
    - Pawling school scene, Route 22, 2
  - Hammersley Hill: Pawling - activities, 1938 - 1939; 6 (Box 1568)
    - Mrs. Wyeth Ray skating winter 38-39 [1938-1939], 1
  - Hammersley Hill: Relatives, circa 1930s; 7 (Box 1568)
    - Mrs. Dr. Thomas [Mrs. Harry Thomas], Pherbia and "Bozo" on the front lawn at Clover Brook Farm, 1
    - Mrs. Dr. Thomas [Mrs. Harry Thomas], Pherbia and "Bozo" on the front lawn at Clover Brook Farm, 2
    - Mrs. Dr. Thomas [Mrs. Harry Thomas] standing beside tree on front lawn, with "Bozo," at Clover Brook, 3
    - Mrs. Dr. Thomas [Mrs. Harry Thomas] standing beside tree on front lawn, with "Bozo," at Clover Brook, 4
    - Janet Smith, Sarah Hogate and a little boy in baseball suit, 5
    - Janet Smith, Sarah Hogate and a little boy in baseball suit, 6
  - Hammersley Hill: Lumberjacks with celebs [celebrities], 1937 - 1938; 8 (Box 1568)
    - Lumberjacks and L.T., Marvin McIntyre, and John Roosevelt at ball field. Summer 1938, 1
    - Lumberjacks with Virginia Moore at barbecue grounds 1937, 2
    - Lumberjacks + Celebs at QHBP [Quaker Hill Ball Park] - Col. [Colonel] Stoop [Stoopnagle], [Marvin] McIntyre, J. [John] Roosevelt, Hawks, Mason, Lehr + Falley, 1937, 3
    - Lumberjacls + Pres. [President Franklin Delano Roosevelt] 1938, 4
    - Lumberjacks and group, Virginia Moore and McClelland Barclay standing on diving boat at dam, 5
    - Limberjacks; Virginia Moore. McClelland Barclay at dam at Clover Brook, 6
    - Lumberjacks and McCleddand Barclay at dam, 7
    - Lumberjacks, L.T. [Lowell Thomas], [Marvin] McIntyre. + John Roosevelt 1937, 8
  - Hammersley Hill: Lumberjacks - miscellaneous, 1937 - 1938; 9 (Box 1568)
    - Lumberjacks and group at dam, 1
    - Lumberjacks and group of boys and girls outsides of gymnasium, 2
    - Lumberjacks and group of boys and girls outsides of gymnasium, 3
    - Lumberjacks and group of boys and girls outsides of gymnasium, 4
    - Lumberjacks and group of boys and girls outsides of gymnasium, 5
    - "Lumberjacks" on hillside above dam at Clover Brook, 6
    - "Lumberjacks" on hillside above dam at Clover Brook, 7
    - Lumberjacks and group at dam, 8
    - Lumberjacks and groups of girls at soft drink stand - - QHBP [Quaker Hill Ball Park], 9
    - Lumberjacks + young ladies QHBP [Mrs. Warrick] top 1938, 10
    - Lumberjacks + group at dam at C.B. [Clover Brook], 11
    - Lumberjacks with Virginia Moore at barbecue pit, 12
    - Lumberjacks, L.T. and L.T., Jr., picture taken at Quaker Lake, 1937, 13
    - "Lumberjacks" at beer well, between ball field and dam at C.B. [Clover Brook], 14
    - Lumberjacks at barbecue pit, 15
  - Hammersley Hill: Lawrence Smith School - teams [negative images distorted], circa 1938; 10 (Box 1568)
    - Lawrence Smith soccer team, 1
    - Lawrence Smith soccer team, 2
    - Lawrence Smith soccer team, 3
    - Lawrence Smith soccer team, 4
    - Lawrence Smith soccer team, 5
    - Lawrence Smith soccer team, 6
  - Hammersley Hill: Lawrence Smith School - outing, 1938; 11 (Box 1568)
    - Mrs. Thomas, scenes at Lawence Smith outing, 1938, 1
    - Mrs. Thomas, scenes at Lawence Smith outing, 1938, 2
    - Mrs. Thomas, scenes at Lawence Smith outing, 1938, 3
    - Mrs. Thomas, scenes at Lawence Smith outing, 1938, 4
    - Mrs. Thomas, scenes at Lawence Smith outing, 1938, 5
    - Mrs. Thomas, scenes at Lawence Smith outing, 1938, 6
    - Mrs. Thomas, scenes at Lawence Smith outing, 1938, 7
  - Hammersley Hill: Miscellaneous family pictures [negative images distorted], circa late 1930s; 12 (Box 1568)
    - Mrs. T [Frances Ryan Thomas] + Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] when Sonny was a small boy, 1
    - Mrs. T [Frances Ryan Thomas] + Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.] when Sonny was a small boy, 2
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], L.T. [Lowell Thomas] + dog, 3
    - Sonny [Lowell Thomas, Jr.], L.T. [Lowell Thomas] + dog, 4
    - L.T. + Sonny skating, 5
    - Mrs. T. [Frances Ryan Thomas], Sonny + dog, 6
    - Mrs. T. [Frances Ryan Thomas], Sonny + dog, 7
    - Mrs. T. [Frances Ryan Thomas], Lowell Thomas, Jr., and others, 8
  - Hammersley Hill: Snake hunt pictures, circa late 1930s; 13 (Box 1568)
    - People all holding live snakes, 1
    - People all holding live snakes, 2
    - People all holding live snakes, 3
    - People all holding live snakes, 4
    - People all holding live snakes, 5
    - People all holding live snakes, 6
  - Hammersley Hill: Miscellaneous activities, 1939; 14 (Box 1568)
    - Byrd banquet scene, Col [Colonel] R., Capt. [Captain] Felix Reisenberg, Admiral Byrd, L.T. [Lowell Thomas] + Dr. Roy Chapman Andrews, 1
    - Scene at banquet for Admiral Byrd, held at the World's Fair, October 27th, 1939 a the Ford Pavillion, 2
    - [Lowell Thomas golfing with 3 men, including Thomas Dewey and perhaps Admiral Dick Byrd], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas in flight gear with 2 men standing near airplane, possibly Admiral Dick Byrd], 4
  - Hammersley Hill: Recreation barn, circa late 1930s; 15 (Box 1568)
    - Fashion show at the Recreation Barn, 1
    - Fashion show at the Recreation Barn, 2
    - Fashion show at the Recreation Barn, 3
    - Fashion show at the Recreation Barn, 4
    - Fashion show at the Recreation Barn, 5
    - Fashion show at the Recreation Barn, 6
    - Fashion show at the Recreation Barn, 7
    - Fashion show at the Recreation Barn, 8
    - Fashion show at the Recreation Barn, 9